couponspot.com 2014-06-29

# Discount Coupon Codes & Shopping Deals | Online Promotional Codes | Free Store Coupons – CouponSpot.com :: Privacy Policy

Visits to CouponSpot.com are monitored for the accumulation of statistical  
information, including, but not limited to, the number of visits to the  
site, the pages people visit, from which domains the visitors come from  
and the browsers people use to visit the site. Such information is  
important to allow CouponSpot.com to evaluate the effectiveness of the  
services it is providing, to monitor its own performance and to make it  
easier for other visitors to use the site.

What Is Covered Under This Privacy Policy?

All personal information you provide directly to CouponSpot.com is covered  
under this privacy policy. This may include, but not be limited to, your  
name, address, date of birth, phone number, e-mail address, other  
financial information, and other personally identifying information.

Postings by users on our forum are not protected under this privacy policy  
and not considered confidential information or confidential communication.  
CouponSpot.com shall have the right , but not the obligation, to monitor  
the content of its bulletin boards, forums and chat rooms to determine  
compliance with CouponSpot.com policies and terms of use and any other  
operating rules established for CouponSpot.com. CouponSpot.com shall have  
the right in its sole discretion, and without prior notice, to edit,  
refuse to post, or remove any materials submitted to or posted to its  
bulletin boards, forums, or chat rooms.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal  
information online - for example on message boards, through e-mail, or in  
chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In  
short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the  
public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.  
CouponSpot.com is not responsible for the disclosure of your information  
under these circumstances and such disclosure is not covered under this  
privacy policy.

Additionally, advertisers and vendors hosted on our site, or who link to  
our site, may collect information about you if you click on their ads,  
visit their web sites, or make a purchase from them. Information collected  
by vendors or advertisers hosted on our site, or who link to our site, is  
not covered under this privacy policy.

Finally, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your  
passwords and/or any account information.  
Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.

What Kind of Information About Me Does CouponSpot.com Collect?

Some personal information is gathered if you register on our site for  
e-mail, contests, promotions, chats, games, access to community sites or  
when you register for any other reason. During registration,  
CouponSpot.com may require you to provide your name, date of birth,  
gender, zip code, country of residence and e-mail address. Additionally,  
CouponSpot.com will ask you to voluntarily provide other information about  
yourself. The more information you volunteer, the better able we are to  
understand who our users are and the better able we are to improve and  
customize our site for you. Once you register on our site for any reason,  
you no longer are anonymous to CouponSpot.com.

In addition to information obtained through registration, CouponSpot.com  
sometimes obtains personal information about you when you make a purchase  
from a store on our site. That information may include, but not be limited  
to, your name, address, e-mail address and what you have purchased.

From time to time, CouponSpot.com will conduct surveys on its site for  
research purposes. When you participate in a survey, the information you  
provide about yourself and the responses to the questions will be  
collected by CouponSpot.com.

If you contact CouponSpot.com, we may keep a record of your identity and  
your correspondence.

CouponSpot.com also tracks and collects your computer's IP address to help  
with system administration and to compile information about traffic  
patterns on the site. IP addresses also may appear in outgoing  
CouponSpot.com web mail message headers. Your computer IP address  
identifies your computer and the network or Internet service provider to  
which your computer is connected.

Cookies and How CouponSpot.com Uses Them

A cookie is a small amount of data that is transferred from a web server  
through your browser and stored on the hard drive of your computer. The  
data in a cookie vary, depending on the reasons for the cookie. For  
example, if you have a special user name and password to log into a part  
of the CouponSpot.com site, such as a chat area, the cookie may contain  
your user name and password so that when you log on, the web server  
recognizes you. CouponSpot.com may use cookies to gather general  
information about its audience and store, measure traffic patterns on the  
site, and track information about you and the way you use the site. As  
CouponSpot.com improves its service and offers its users more ability to  
customize their experience and the content they view, cookies may be used  
to assist in that personalization process.

Advertisers on CouponSpot.com may also use their own cookies.

You do not have to permit the use of cookies. You can, through the options  
in your web browser, choose to accept all cookies, choose to reject all  
cookies or choose to receive notification when a cookie is being delivered  
so that you can make a decision whether to accept each cookie on a  
case-by-case basis. If you refuse all cookies, or refuse particular  
cookies, you will not be able to use some of the features of  
CouponSpot.com, including, but not limited to, web e-mail, chats, opinion  
polls, and personalized or customized features.

How Is My Information Used by CouponSpot.com?

Personal information collected from you at CouponSpot.com, as well as  
information about traffic patterns and user behavior on the site, is used  
primarily for these purposes:

):    1\. To conduct internal research. We constantly are assessing who is  
using our site and how they are using it. This assists us in making  
decisions about how to improve the site and to better serve our users.  
Research data are aggregated and do not include data about specific  
individuals. We may share aggregated research (but not individual user  
information) with our advertisers or business partners. Additionally,  
CouponSpot.com may, at some time, use your personal information to contact  
you and ask if you would be willing to participate in a focus group,  
survey, or some other type of research effort.

   2\. To customize or personalize your experience at CouponSpot.com. As  
CouponSpot.com improves its service, it will offer users more  
opportunities to customize content and other aspects of the site.  
Personal information provided by you will be used to assist in the  
customization process.

   3\. To tailor advertising efforts. Most of the information and services  
available to you at CouponSpot.com are free. In order to continue  
providing services free of charge, CouponSpot.com sells advertising.  
Advertisers prefer to target their efforts toward to audiences who  
more likely will be interested in their product. Your personal  
information helps us tell advertisers in general terms how many people  
are using our site and the demographic attributes of the people using  
different parts of our site. This helps the advertisers and  
CouponSpot.com make a better decision about where to most effectively  
place advertising on the site. We never provide information about  
individual users to advertisers. However, if you choose to make a  
purchase from an advertiser on our site, that advertiser may collect  
personal information about you during the purchase process.

With Whom Will You Share My Individual Information?

CouponSpot.com will strive to maintain the confidentiality of all personal  
user information and communications which are transmitted directly to  
CouponSpot.com. However, CouponSpot.com reserves the right to disclose any  
of your personal information under special circumstances. These  
circumstances include:

1\. When we believe in good faith that the law requires such disclosure.

2\. When disclosing such information is necessary to identify, contact or  
initiate legal action against someone violating CouponSpot.com's Terms of  
Service, or someone who is causing injury to or interference with  
CouponSpot.com's rights or property, other CouponSpot.com users, or anyone  
else who can be harmed by such activities.

   3\. When we must disclose such information for administrative and other  
purposes necessary to maintain and improve our product and services.

When you provide personal information on CouponSpot.com, it is being used  
by CouponSpot.com alone, unless specifically stated otherwise. In some  
cases, we may be providing a service to you or a promotion that is being  
made available with the assistance of another company. If that is the  
case, there may be instances when we must share your information with our  
partner company to facilitate the co-branded service or promotion. If your  
information is to be shared with a partner company, you will be notified  
prior to the transfer of that information to the partner company and you  
will be given the option of not permitting the transfer of your  
information to that partner company.

When CouponSpot.com conducts research about the use of its site, it may  
hire a professional research firm to assist in that process. Information  
about you may be shared with that research firm and that firm may contact  
you to ask your opinions about CouponSpot.com or to see if you are  
interested in participating in a research activity for CouponSpot.com,  
such as a focus group or survey. The research firm will be bound by its  
contract with CouponSpot.com to use your information strictly for  
CouponSpot.com research purposes, to keep your information confidential,  
and to adequately secure or destroy its records of your information when  
the research is complete so that information cannot be obtained by others.

Once again, please be aware that advertisers and vendors hosted on our  
site, or who link to our site, may collect information about you through  
their own cookies if you click on their ads or if you make a purchase from  
them. This includes the purchase of classified or personal advertisements.  
Information collected by vendors or advertisers on our site, or who link  
to our site, is not covered under this privacy policy.

Various web sites collect user information and create lists and/or  
databases of this user information. These lists or databases are sometimes  
sold to third parties under contractual agreements that place limits on  
how the purchasing parties can reuse the information. Currently,  
CouponSpot.com does not sell information about its users to third parties  
for any reason. If CouponSpot.com chooses to do so in the future, it will  
notify users of CouponSpot.com of its intentions and give users the option  
to exclude their information from any such lists or databases sold to  
third parties.

Contacting The Web Site

If you have any questions about our privacy policy or the privacy  
practices of this site, please contact us at support@CouponSpot.com. We  
will be happy to answer your question.
